{ "public" : true, "front" : "Name, author, year", "back" : "Starry night,Vincent van Gogh,1889", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/TY5QEmnER56rN1KRMmvf", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "5SPW4J3f4DWQFcuSA" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, author, year", "back" : "Guernica,Pablo Picasso,1937", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/l9pcjjwSSkCKBVLQaYKX", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "PDqbRSHCpj9LN4oTK" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, artist, year", "back" : "Whistler's Mother,James NcNeill Whistler,1871", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/HwuwD8X4TcymOhycoF3Q", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "SSQurbnLsKDfCiN59" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, author, year", "back" : "The Persistence of Memory,Salvador Dali,1931", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/xka8H3AFQI2MpvPXZXyM", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "iPsyu5DwvjQNomREx" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, year, artist", "back" : "Girl with a Pearl Earring1665Johannes Vermeer", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/WoKmktC0Rh6eVzKvufjN", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "pe2HKBwk9JZp5JAq8" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, artist, year", "back" : "The Kiss,Gustav Klimt,1908", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/jz1A2o22RCSmr5rl7JWF", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "qQ7fJ9iPakiiWcK43" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, artist, year", "back" : "The Night Watch,Rembrand,1642", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/HZeZ3POMQx2UNGmBCM5j", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "ryqbDzaC5jydiG3hG" },
{ "_id" : "sfwjHM9ZfGkLW5knf", "back" : "The Mona Lisa,Leonardo da Vinci,1503-1519", "backPicture" : null, "comments" : [], "downVotes" : [], "front" : "Name, artist, years", "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/UjArMGP0QVSs5kqyOZlw", "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "previousVersions" : [ { "_id" : "6389810c4dcb1756636a39aa", "front" : "Name, author, years", "back" : "The Mona Lisa,Leonardo da Vinci,1503-1519", "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/UjArMGP0QVSs5kqyOZlw", "backPicture" : null, "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "score" : 0 } ], "public" : true, "reason" : "Rewording the front", "score" : 0, "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "upVotes" : [], "updatedBy" : "TYMaLrb495sKhfFh4", "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "version" : 2 },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, author, year", "back" : "A Sunday Afternoon on the Island of La Grande Jatte,Georges Seurat,1884", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/LmbrvaRMiB2xAxMtQMEg", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "vQuA5hkyJ4exwgfo7" },
{ "public" : true, "front" : "Title, author, year", "back" : "The Scream,Edvard Munch,1893", "source" : { "youtube" : "", "wikipedia" : "", "link" : "", "khan" : "", "other" : "" }, "frontPicture" : "https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/ZAiIsiK5RWyJOEbEMFVx", "backPicture" : null, "user" : "F6FgiJCssXvguDMPw", "previousVersions" : [], "upVotes" : [], "downVotes" : [], "comments" : [], "version" : 1, "reason" : null, "score" : 0, "updatedBy" : null, "lessons" : [ { "course" : "4JoC9MRJuMfsjXyia", "lesson" : "0e8f13f10b3f82c3cb39b15e" } ], "_id" : "xYi82cywPoRyKo4HY" },
